gaininggreen.com 2016-06-27

# Privacy Policy | Gaining Green

**Your Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

 **Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/) Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, gaininggreen has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

 **Collection of Personal Information**

When visiting gaininggreen, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

 **Links to third party Websites**

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

 **Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.  
If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of gaininggreen then you may contact us at editor@gaininggreen.com

The disclaimer is to be read and fully understood before using our site, or joining our email list. Never invest in any stock featured on our site or emails unless you can afford to lose your entire investment.

Release of Liability: Through use of this website viewing or using you agree to hold Gaininggreen.com which is owned and operated by gaininggreen.com and its operators owners and employees harmless and to completely release them from any and all liability due to any and all loss (monetary or otherwise), damage (monetary or otherwise), or injury (monetary or otherwise) that you may incur. Gaininggreen.com is written and published by Gaininggreen.com employees. Readers are advised that this analysis report is issued solely for informational purposes. Neither the information presented nor any statement or expression of opinion, or any other matter herein, directly or indirectly constitutes a representation by the publisher nor a solicitation of the purchase or sale of any securities. The information contained herein is based on sources which we believe to be reliable but is not guaranteed by us as being accurate and does not purport to be a complete statement or summary of the available data. The owner, publisher, editor and their associates are not responsible for errors and omissions. They may from time to time have a position in the securities mentioned herein and may increase or decrease such positions without notice. Any opinions expressed are subject to change without notice. Gaininggreen.com encourages readers and investors to supplement the information in these reports with independent research and other professional advice. Information can and will be sold such as email addresses, names and phone numbers.

All information on featured companies is provided by the companies profiled, or is available from public sources and Gaininggreen.com makes no representations, warranties or guarantees as to the accuracy or completeness of the disclosure by the profiled companies. Gaininggreen.com, nor any of its affiliates are not registered investment advisors or a broker dealers. Gaininggreen.com has been advised that the investments in companies profiled are considered to be high risk and use of the information provided is at the investor’s sole risk. Gaininggreen.com has also been advised that the purchase of such high risk securities may result in the loss of some or all of the investment. Investors should not rely solely on the information presented. Rather, investors should use the information provided by the profiled companies as a starting point for doing additional independent research on the profiled companies in order to allow the investor to form his or her own opinion regarding investing in the profiled companies. Factual statements made by the profiled companies are made as of the date stated and are subject to change without notice. Investing in micro-cap securities is highly speculative and carries an extremely high degree of risk. It is possible that an investor’s entire investment may be lost or impaired due to the speculative nature of the companies profiled. Gaininggreen.com makes no recommendation that the securities of the companies profiled should be purchased, sold or held by individuals or entities that learn of the profiled companies through Gaininggreen.com. Gaininggreen.com owners may or may not hold positions in the companies that are profiled. Investing in securities is highly speculative and carries an extremely high degree of risk. It is possible that an investor’s investment may be lost or impaired due to the speculative nature of the companies profiled.

The information contained herein contains forward-looking information within the meaning of Section 27A of the Securities Act of 1993 and Section 21E of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 including statements regarding expected continual growth of the company and the value of its securities. In accordance with the safe harbor provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act of 1995 it is hereby noted that statements contained herein that look forward in time which include everything other than historical information, involve risk and uncertainties that may affect the company’s actual results of operation. Factors that could cause actual results to differ include the size and growth of the market for the company’s products, the company’s ability to fund its capital requirements in the near term and in the long term, pricing pressures, unforeseen and/or unexpected circumstances in happenings, pricing pressures, etc. Investing in securities is speculative and carries risk. Past performance does not guarantee future results.

Third Party Web Sites and Information Gaininggreen.com and newsletter may provide hyperlinks to third party websites or access to third party content. Gaininggreen.com does not control, endorse, or guarantee content found in such sites. You agree that Gaininggreen.com is not responsible for any content, associated links, resources, or services associated with a third party site. You further agree that Gaininggreen.com. shall not be liable for any loss or damage of any sort associated with your use of third party content. Links and access to these sites are provided for your convenience only.

Forward Looking Statements  
Information in our emails and on Gaininggreen.com will contain “forward looking statements” as defined under Section 27A of the Securities Act of 1933 and Section 21B of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934. An example of forward-looking information are statements relating to the future anticipated direction of the industry, plans for future expansion, various business development activities, planned capital expenditures, future funding sources, anticipated sales growth and potential contracts. These and similar forward statements are subject to a number of known and unknown risks and uncertainties outside our control that could cause actual operations or results to differ materially from those anticipated.  
The cautionary statements made in this document should be read as being applicable to all related forward-looking statements wherever they appear on Gaininggreen.com or in other communications.  
We encourage you to visit the Securities Exchanges Commission Web site [http://www.sec.gov](http://www.sec.gov/) and read about how to avoid Internet Scams and other valuable information.  
Compensation  
In order to be in full compliance with the Securities Act of 1933, Section 17(b), Gaininggreen.com and its management fully disclose that they receive fees from profiled companies or agents representing the profiled companies. These fees may be paid in cash, securities of profiled companies, or both, and will be completely disclosed in each profile.  
Regarding the marketing programs that Gaininggreen.com has been compensated for providing investor awareness:  
Gaininggreen.com receives compensation and its employees, affiliates, or members of their families will hold stock in the profiled companies, there is an inherent conflict of interest in the statements and opinions, and such statements and opinions are not independent.  
Risks Involved  
Gaininggreen.com will not be responsible for or accept any liability for any losses arising from an investor’s reliance on or use of this assembled information. This assembled information is for information purposes only, and is neither a solicitation to buy nor an offer to sell securities. All assembled information provided is for informational purposes only and is not intended to be used as the sole source of information on a company.  
Gaininggreen.com disseminates information to those who wish to receive it. Small-cap and Penney stocks are considered to be highly speculative and may be unsuitable for all but very aggressive investors. Small-cap companies, micro-cap companies, penny stocks and/or thinly traded securities are inherently risky and volatile investments. You should be prepared to lose some or all of the money you invest. While historical data may be informative and positive, it should be understood there is no guarantee that past performance will be indicative of future results. It is often very difficult if not impossible to buy at our exact pick prices and/or sell exactly at their highs.  
Buying and selling of shares  
Gaininggreen.com and its affiliates or officers will buy, hold, or sell shares, of mentioned Companies, in the open market without notice. Gaininggreen.com and its affiliates will sell its shares in the event the shares rise in value, and in most cases will sell its shares for less than target prices. Gaininggreen.com and its affiliates will not advise as to when it decides to sell and does not and will not offer any opinion as to when others should sell; each person must make that decision based on their judgment.  
PLEASE always do your own due diligence, and consult your financial advisor.

Name and emails entered can be sold also by signing up you will receive third party offers.
